<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Applied Machine Learning on Machine Learning for Educational Data Science</title>
    <link>https://ml-21.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Applied Machine Learning on Machine Learning for Educational Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ml-21.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homework Assignment 1</title>
      <link>https://ml-21.netlify.app/hw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-21.netlify.app/hw1/</guid>
      <description>Overview The purpose of this lab is to get you working with git and GitHub collaboratively, as well as to refresh some basic {dplyr} skills. You should work together in groups of 3-4.
The basics of the lab are to:
 Create a shared repo Create an R Markdown document Work on a few different data visualizations together  File issues for the different pieces of the lab Create branches for those issues Different people work on different branches - merge them in when you&amp;rsquo;re ready   Submit a link to the repo through Canvas when you&amp;rsquo;ve completed the lab I check the commit history, and give each person credit  To receive full credit you must create and merge branches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assignments</title>
      <link>https://ml-21.netlify.app/assignments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-21.netlify.app/assignments/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://ml-21.netlify.app/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-21.netlify.app/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Supplemental Resources Each of the below links to the full book. Icons in the schedule link to specific chapters. All books except two are freely available from the provided links. Applied Predictive Modeling is available online through UO Libraries. Mathematics for Machine Learning is not necessary for this course; however, I provide the link in case anybody is interested. A shorter version of similar content is freely available.
Mathematics for Machine LearningDeisenroth, A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://ml-21.netlify.app/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ml-21.netlify.app/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Below are the meeting times for our class
 Term: Fall 2021 Time: Monday/Wednesday, 12:00-13:20 Classroom: TBD Instructor: Cengiz Zopluoglu  email: (preferred contact method) cengiz@uoregon.edu office hours: TBD pronouns: he/him/his    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
